http://www.miramax.com/termsofuse/#privacy

Miramax.com Terms of Use
Welcome to Miramax.com, a Miramax Film NY, LLC ("Miramax") Web site (our "Site"). Thank you for visiting, and we know that the interactive media on our Site will provide you with many engaging and entertaining opportunities to explore all that is Miramax.
Our Site showcases Miramax's highly acclaimed catalogue of films, televisions shows and other audio visual entertainment. It is important to us that you, and our other visitors, have the best possible time while using our Site and that when you use this Site you are fully aware of your respective legal rights and obligations. For that reason, we have created these Terms of Use as the legally binding terms to govern your use of this Site. Please read these Terms of Use carefully before using our Site, because they affect your legal rights and obligations.
Your Acceptance of Terms
These Terms of Use govern your use of our Site, including all features and functionalities, instant streaming downloads, user interfaces, and all content and software associated therewith. By using, visiting, browsing or downloading any content or accessing any part of our Site, you accept and agree to be bound by these Terms of Use. If you do not agree to these Terms of Use, do not use our Site.
Some areas of this Site may be subject to additional terms and conditions, which you should read carefully before making any use of those areas. Such additional terms will not change or replace these Terms of Use regarding use of this Site, unless otherwise expressly stated.
Please note that these Terms of Use may be revised and reissued without notice at any time by updating this posting. You should visit this page regularly to review the current Terms of Use.
Your continued use of our Site will be deemed as irrevocable acceptance of any revisions.
How To Contact Us
This Site is controlled and operated by Miramax Film NY, LLC, located at 1901 Avenue of the Stars, Suite 2000, Los Angeles, California 90067.
Please forward any comments or complaints about our Site and any questions regarding privacy or legal matters to legal@miramax.com.
Your Registration
To access this Site or some of the resources it has to offer, you may be asked to provide registration details. It is a condition of use of this Site that all the details you provide be true and accurate.
To access this Site or some of the resources it has to offer, you may be asked to provide registration details. It is a condition of use of this Site that all the details you provide be correct, current, and complete. If we at Miramax believe the details are not correct, current, or complete, we have the right to refuse you access to our Site, or any of its resources, and to terminate or suspend your account. You are responsible for updating and maintaining the truth and accuracy of the information you provide to us relating to your account.
Unless we have received a properly completed and acceptable parental consent form governing your use of this Site, we will assume (and by using this Site you warrant that) you have legal capacity to enter into the agreement set out in these Terms of Use (i.e., that you are of sufficient age and mental capacity and are otherwise entitled to be legally bound in contract).
Online Privacy Notice
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide a notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this site. Click here to show this notice, which forms part of these Terms of Use.
Trademarks and Copyrights
This Site and materials incorporated and/or made available by streaming and/or download by Miramax on this Site ("Material") are protected by copyrights, patents, trade secrets or other proprietary rights ("Copyrights").
Some of the characters, logos or other images incorporated by Miramax on this Site are also protected as registered or unregistered trademarks, trade names and/or service marks owned by Miramax or others ("Trademarks").
Miramax respects the intellectual property rights of others and asks users of this Site to do the same.
Your Use of Material
Your right to make use of this Site and any Material or other content appearing on it is subject to your compliance with these Terms of Use. Modification retransmission, authorized downloading, copying or use of the Material or any other content on this Site for any purpose not permitted by these Terms of Use may be a violation of the Copyrights and/or Trademarks and is prohibited.
You may access and display Material and all other content displayed on this Site for non-commercial, personal, entertainment use on a single computer only. The Material and all other content on this Site may not otherwise be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted, distributed or used in any way unless specifically authorized by Miramax. Any authorization to copy Material granted by Miramax in any part of this Site for any reason is restricted to making a single copy for non-commercial, personal, entertainment use on a single computer only, and is subject to your keeping intact all copyright and other proprietary notices. Using any Material on any other web site or networked computer environment is prohibited. Also, decompiling, reverse engineering, disassembling, or otherwise reducing the Material or code used in any software on this Site into a readable form in order to examine the construction of such software and/or to copy or create other products based (in whole or in part) on such software, is prohibited.
THIRD PARTY LINKS
Our Sites may link to and/or contain advertisements about non-Miramax owned or controlled Web sites or other Internet or mobile resources. You acknowledge and understand that Miramax does not endorse or sponsor such other third party Web sites or other Internet resources and Miramax EXPRESSLY AND SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIMS ANY RESPONSIBILITY AND LIABILITY FOR ANY CONTENT, SOFTWARE, FUNCTIONALITY, SERVICES OR ADVERTISED PRODUCTS OR SERVICES FOUND ON OR RELATED TO ANY SUCH THIRD PARTY WEB SITE OR OTHER INTERNET OR MOBILE RESOURCES.
Disclaimer of Warranties
YOUR USE OF THIS SITE IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. OUR SITE AND ALL THE MATERIALS, INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, FACILITIES, SERVICES AND OTHER CONTENT IN OUR SITE ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE" WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMISSIBLE PURSUANT TO APPLICABLE LAW, OUR SITE, MIRAMAX AND ANY SUBSIDIARIES OR AFFILIATED COMPANIES OF MIRAMAX DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. MIRAMAX DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE FUNCTIONS CONTAINED IN THIS SITE WILL BE AVAILABLE, UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE, THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED, OR THAT OUR SITE OR THE SERVERS THAT MAKE OUR SITE AVAILABLE ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS. MIRAMAX DOES NOT WARRANT OR MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING THE USE OR THE RESULTS OF THE USE OF THE MATERIAL, INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, FACILITIES, SERVICES OR OTHER CONTENT IN OUR SITE OR ANY WEB SITES LINKED TO OUR SITE IN TERMS OF THEIR CORRECTNESS, ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, OR OTHERWISE.
MIRAMAX MAKES NO WARRANTIES THAT YOUR USE OF THE MATERIALS, INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, FACILITIES, SERVICE OR OTHER CONTENT IN OUR SITE OR ANY WEB SITE WILL NOT INFRINGE THE RIGHTS OF OTHERS AND MIRAMAX ASSUMES NO LIABILITY OR RESPONSIBILITY FOR ERRORS OR OMISSIONS IN SUCH MATERIALS, INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, FACILITIES, SERVICE OR OTHER CONTENT OF OUR SITE OR ANY OTHER WEB SITE. IF APPLICABLE LAW DOES NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF SOME OR ALL OF THE ABOVE IMPLIED WARRANTIES TO APPLY TO YOU, THE ABOVE EXCLUSIONS WILL APPLY TO YOU ONLY TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW.
Limitation of Liability
Miramax DISCLAIMS ALL LIABILITY WHETHER BASED IN CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE), STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE, AND DOES NOT ACCEPT ANY LIABILITY FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE (DIRECT, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, ACTUAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY OR OTHERWISE) RESULTING FROM ANY USE OF, OR INABILITY TO USE, OUR SITE OR ANY OTHER WEB SITE, OR THE MATERIAL, INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, FACILITIES, SERVICES OR OTHER CONTENT ON OUR SITE OR ANY OTHER WEB SITE, REGARDLESS OF THE BASIS UPON WHICH LIABILITY IS CLAIMED AND EVEN IF ANY MEMBER OF MIRAMAX HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH LOSS OR DAMAGE. WITHOUT LIMITATION, YOU (AND NOT ANY MEMBER OF MIRAMAX) ASSUME THE ENTIRE COST OF ALL NECESSARY SERVICING, REPAIR OR CORRECTION IN THE EVENT OF ANY SUCH LOSS OR DAMAGE ARISING.
IF APPLICABLE LAW DOES NOT ALLOW ALL OR ANY PART OF THE ABOVE LIMITATION OF LIABILITY TO APPLY TO YOU, THE LIMITATIONS WILL APPLY TO YOU ONLY TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW.
Specifically, Miramax assumes no liability or responsibility for any: (i) errors, mistakes, or inaccuracies of content; (ii) personal injury or property damage, of any nature whatsoever, resulting from your access to or use of our Site (or any parts thereof); (iii) any unauthorized access to or use of Miramax's secure servers and/or any and all personal information stored therein; (iv) any interruption or cessation of transmission to or from our Site; (v) any bugs, viruses, Trojan horses, or the like which may be transmitted to or through our Site (or any parts thereof) by any third party; and/or (vi) for any loss or damage of any kind incurred as a result of the use of any Invited Submissions (hereinafter defined)and/or other Site content posted, shared, forwarded, emailed, transmitted, or otherwise made available on or by means of our Site and/or otherwise through your or any other Site users' exercise of any rights under any of the Licenses granted by Miramax herein. Miramax reserves the right, in its sole and exclusive discretion, to change, modify, add, remove or disable access to any portion of our Site (including, without limitation any of our Site Services).
Forums
THE MATERIALS, INFORMATION AND OPINIONS INCLUDED AND/OR EXPRESSED IN OR ON BULLETIN BOARDS, CHAT ROOMS, COMMUNITY PAGES OR OTHER FORUMS ON THIS SITE ("FORUMS") ARE NOT NECESSARILY THOSE OF MIRAMAX, PARENTS, SUBSIDIARIES, AFFILIATES, SUCCESSORS, LICENSEES, ASSIGNS OR CONTENT PROVIDERS. MIRAMAX DOES NOT UNDERTAKE TO MONITOR OR REVIEW FORUMS AND THE CONTENT OF FORUMS IS NOT THE RESPONSIBILITY OF MIRAMAX.
MIRAMAX MAY REMOVE OR MODIFY ANY CONTENT WITHOUT NOTICE OR LIABILITY AT ANY TIME IN MIRAMAX'S SOLE DISCRETION. ANY USE OF THE FORUMS WILL BE AT YOUR OWN RISK AND WILL BE SUBJECT TO THE DISCLAIMERS AND LIMITATIONS ON LIABILITY SET OUT ABOVE.
Blog
MIRAMAX MAY POST CONTENT INCLUDING ARTICLES, PHOTOS, VIDEOS, TEXT EXCERPTS, QUOTES OR OTHER CONTENT ("BLOG CONTENT") IN THE BLOG SECTION OF THIS SITE THAT INCLUDES VIEWS AND/OR OPINIONS.
THE VIEWS AND/OR OPINIONS EXPRESSED IN THIS BLOG CONTENT ARE NOT NECESSARILY THOSE OF MIRAMAX OR OUR AFFILIATES AND OUR INCLUSION OF THIS BLOG CONTENT ON OUR SITE DOES NOT IN ANY WAY IMPLY AGREEMENT OR SUPPORT OF THE OPINIONS AND/OR VIEWS EXPRESSED THEREIN.
Non-Solicitation Policy
It is Miramax's policy not to accept or consider unsolicited creative materials, ideas, or suggestions. This is to avoid any misunderstandings if your materials, ideas, or suggestions are similar or identical to those we have developed independently. Accordingly, please do not submit to us any unsolicited screenplays, treatments, synopses, concept footage, stories, ideas, samples, mock-ups, original artwork or other original creative materials or suggestions. Any such submissions shall be considered non-confidential and non-proprietary, and will be returned to the sender, or deleted or discarded, without being reviewed.
If you nevertheless choose to ignore our policy and submit any materials to us, you acknowledge that you have read Miramax’s submission policy and that by making such a submission, you understand that Miramax has no obligation to you for your submission and that you have no claim whatsoever based on such submission.
System Abuse
Without limitation, you agree not to send, create or reply to so called "mailbombs" (i.e., emailing copies of a single message to many users, or sending large or multiple files or messages to a single user with malicious intent) or engage in "spamming"(i.e., unsolicited emailing for business or other purposes) or undertake any other activity which may adversely effect the operation or enjoyment of this Site by any other person.
You may not reproduce, sell, resell or otherwise exploit any resource, or access to any resource, contained on this Site.
Security
Any usernames and passwords used for this Site are for individual use only. You shall be responsible for the security of your username and password (if any).
Miramax shall be entitled to monitor your username and password and, at its discretion, require you to change it. If you use a username and password that Miramax considers insecure, Miramax will be entitled to require this to be changed and/or terminate your account.
You are prohibited from using any services or facilities provided in connection with this Site to compromise security or tamper with system resources and/or accounts. The use or distribution of tools designed for compromising security (e.g. password guessing programs, cracking tools or network probing tools) are strictly prohibited. If you become involved in any violation of system security, Miramax reserves the right to release your details to system administrators at other sites in order to assist them in resolving security incidents.
Investigations
Miramax reserves the right to investigate suspected violations of these Terms of Use, including without limitation any violation arising from any submission, posting or e-mails you make or send to any Forum. Miramax may seek to gather information from the user who is suspected of violating these Terms of Use, and from any other user.
Miramax may suspend any users whose conduct or postings are under investigation and may remove such material from its servers as it deems appropriate and without notice. If
Miramax believes, in its sole discretion, that a violation of these Terms of Use has occurred, it may edit or modify any submission, posting or e-mails, remove the material permanently, cancel postings, warn users, suspend users and passwords, terminate accounts or take other corrective action it deems appropriate. Miramax will fully cooperate with any law enforcement authorities or court order requesting or directing Miramax to disclose the identity of anyone posting any e-mails, or publishing or otherwise making available any materials that are believed to violate these Terms of Use. BY ACCEPTING THIS AGREEMENT YOU WAIVE AND HOLD HARMLESS ALL MEMBERS OF MIRAMAX FROM ANY CLAIMS RESULTING FROM ANY ACTION TAKEN BY ANY MEMBER OF MIRAMAX DURING OR AS A RESULT OF ITS INVESTIGATIONS AND/OR FROM ANY ACTIONS TAKEN AS A CONSEQUENCE OF INVESTIGATIONS BY EITHER A MEMBER OF MIRAMAX OR LAW ENFORCEMENT AUTHORITIES.
Service
In order to use this Site, you must obtain access to the World Wide Web and pay any service fee associated with that access. You will need to provide all equipment necessary to connect to our Site on the World Wide Web (including a computer, modem and/or other access devices).
Miramax reserves the right to modify or discontinue, temporarily or permanently, all or any part of this Site and/or any software, facilities and services on this Site, with or without notice, and/or to establish general guidelines and limitations on their use.
Local Regulations
Miramax makes no representation that Materials or other content in our Site are appropriate or available for use outside the United States, its territories, possessions and protectorates. If you choose to access our Site from other locations you do so on your own initiative and at your own risk.
You are responsible for complying with local laws, if and to the extent local laws are applicable. You specifically agree to comply with all applicable laws concerning the transmission of technical data exported from the United States or the country you reside in.
Indemnity
You agree to indemnify and hold harmless Miramax and its affiliates and its and their respective officers, directors, employees, representatives, licensees, authorized designees, successors and assigns from any and all claims, liabilities, damages, losses, costs, expenses, fees (including reasonable outside attorneys' fees and costs) that such parties may incur as a result of or arising from (i) any of your Invited Submissions; (ii) your exercise of any of your rights granted under the Licenses without your compliance with your responsibilities set forth in these Terms; (iii) the breach of any of your warranties, representations, covenants, responsibilities or other obligations set forth in these Terms; (iv) your violation of any person's intellectual property, privacy, publicity or other right; (v) the violation of any Applicable Laws and/or these Terms by you and/or anyone using your registered account to access and/or otherwise use our Site (in whole or in part); or (vi) your willful misconduct or the willful misconduct of anyone accessing our Site through your registered account, in connection with your (and/or such other person's) use of our Site (in whole or in part). Miramax reserves the right to assume the exclusive defense and control of any matter otherwise subject to indemnification by you, in which event you will cooperate with Miramax in asserting any available defenses. This provision shall remain in full force and effect notwithstanding any termination of your use of our Site.
Third-Party Sites
This Site may link you to other sites on the Internet. These sites may contain information or material that some people may find inappropriate or offensive. These other sites are not under the control of Miramax, and you acknowledge that (whether or not such sites are affiliated in any way with Miramax) Miramax is not responsible for the accuracy, copyright compliance, legality, decency, or any other aspect of the content of such sites and Miramax EXPRESSLY AND SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIMS ANY RESPONSIBILITY AND LIABILITY FOR ANY CONTENT, SOFTWARE, FUNCTIONALITY, SERVICES OR ADVERTISED PRODUCTS OR SERVICES FOUND ON OR RELATED TO ANY SUCH THIRD PARTY WEB SITE OR OTHER INTERNET OR MOBILE RESOURCES.
The inclusion of such a link does not imply endorsement of any site by Miramax or any association with its operators.
Miramax cannot ensure that you will be satisfied with any products or services that you purchase from any third-party site that links to or from Miramax because other shop channels are owned and operated by independent retailers. Miramax does not endorse any of the merchandise, nor has Miramax taken any steps to confirm the accuracy or reliability of any of the information contained in such third-party sites. Miramax does not make any representations or warranties as to the security of any information (including, without limitation, credit card and other personal information) you might be requested to give any third party, and you irrevocably waive any claim against us with respect to such sites. We strongly encourage you to make whatever investigation you feel necessary or appropriate before proceeding with any online transaction with any of these third parties.
Proprietary Online Services
Any area of this Site that is accessed through any proprietary online service is subject to the rules, policies and guidelines of such proprietary online service.
Jurisdictional Issues
The Materials and all other content in this Site are presented solely for the purpose of providing entertainment and information and promoting programs, films, music, and other products available in the United States, its territories, possessions, and protectorates.
These Terms of Use shall be governed by, construed and enforced in accordance with the laws of the State of California, as they are applied to agreements entered into and to be performed entirely within California.
Any dispute of any kind between you and any member of Miramax arising under these Terms of Use shall be resolved by binding arbitration in Los Angeles, California, pursuant to the JAMS Streamlined Arbitration Rules and Procedures (see Binding Arbitration Section below).
If any provision of these Terms of Use shall be unlawful, void, or for any reason unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable for this agreement and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions. This is the entire agreement between the parties relating to the matters contained herein.
Claims of Infringement
If you believe a work has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please send Miramax's copyright agent, at the address set forth below, a notification of claimed infringement (an "Infringement Notification") that contains all the following information: (i) identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed; (ii) identification of the claimed infringing material and information reasonably sufficient to permit Miramax to locate the material on our Site; (iii) information reasonably sufficient to permit Miramax to contact you, such as an address, telephone number, and, if available, an e-mail address; (iv) a statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; (v) a statement by you, made under penalty of perjury, that the above information in your notification is accurate and that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright owner's behalf; and (vi) your physical or electronic signature.
Miramax Film NY, LLC
1901 Avenue of the Stars, Suite 2000
Los Angeles, California 90067
Tel:
(310) 409-4321
Attention:
legal@miramax.com
Miramax seeks to preserve any and all exemptions from liability that may be available under the copyright law, but does not necessarily stipulate that it is a service provider as defined in USC section 512(c) or elsewhere.
By submitting an Infringement Notification, you acknowledge and agree that Miramax may forward your Infringement Notification and any related communications to any users who posted the material identified in such notice.
If you believe that your User Submission has been wrongfully removed from our Site, you may send Miramax a counter notification. Pursuant to federal law you may be held liable for damages if you make material misrepresentations in a counter notification. In compliance with Title 17 of the U.S. Code, Section 512, your counter notification, to be effective, must be in writing, sent to Miramax's designated copyright agent, and include substantially the following information: (i) your physical or electronic signature; (ii) identification of the material that has been removed or to which access has been disabled and the location where the material previously appeared on our Site; (iii) a statement under penalty of perjury that you have a good faith belief that the material was removed or disabled as a result of mistake or misidentification of the material to be removed or disabled; and (iv) your name, address, and telephone number and a statement that you consent to the jurisdiction of the Federal District Court in the district in which your address is located (or in the Central District of California, for addresses outside the USA) and agree to accept service of process from the person who submitted the original Infringement Notification that resulted in your User Submission being removed (or an agent of such person) in the event he or she elects to file suit. By submitting a counter notification, you acknowledge and agree that Miramax may forward your counter notification and any related communications to the person who submitted the original Infringement Notification that resulted in the removal of your User Submission or to other third parties.
BINDING ARBITRATION
THESE TERMS SHALL BE CONSTRUED AND ENFORCED IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE LAWS OF THE STATE OF CALIFORNIA AND THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA WITHOUT REGARD TO ANY CHOICE OF LAW OR CONFLICT OF LAWS PRINCIPLES, REGARDLESS OF WHERE YOU LIVE. ALL ACTIONS OR PROCEEDINGS ARISING IN CONNECTION WITH, TOUCHING UPON OR RELATING TO THESE TERMS, OR OUR SITE, OR THE BREACH OF THESE TERMS AND/OR THE SCOPE OF THE PROVISIONS OF THIS ARBITRATION CLAUSE, SHALL BE SUBMITTED TO JAMS ("JAMS") FOR FINAL AND BINDING ARBITRATION UNDER ITS STREAMLINED ARBITRATION RULES, TO BE HELD IN LOS ANGELES COUNTY, CALIFORNIA, BEFORE A SINGLE ARBITRATOR WHO SHALL BE A RETIRED JUDGE, IN ACCORDANCE WITH CALIFORNIA CODE OF CIVIL PROCEDURE §§ 1280 ET SEQ. THE ARBITRATOR SHALL BE SELECTED BY MUTUAL AGREEMENT OF THE PARTIES OR, IF THE PARTIES CANNOT AGREE, THEN BY STRIKING FROM A LIST OF ARBITRATORS SUPPLIED BY JAMS. THE ARBITRATION SHALL BE A CONFIDENTIAL PROCEEDING, CLOSED TO THE GENERAL PUBLIC. THE ARBITRATOR SHALL ISSUE A WRITTEN OPINION STATING THE ESSENTIAL FINDINGS AND CONCLUSIONS UPON WHICH THE ARBITRATOR'S AWARD IS BASED. THE ARBITRATOR SHALL HAVE THE POWER TO ENTER TEMPORARY RESTRAINING ORDERS AND PRELIMINARY AND PERMANENT INJUNCTIONS. NEITHER PARTY SHALL BE ENTITLED OR PERMITTED TO COMMENCE OR MAINTAIN ANY ACTION IN A COURT OF LAW WITH RESPECT TO ANY MATTER IN DISPUTE UNTIL SUCH MATTER SHALL HAVE BEEN SUBMITTED TO ARBITRATION AS HEREIN PROVIDED AND THEN ONLY FOR THE ENFORCEMENT OF THE ARBITRATOR'S AWARD.
This provision shall remain in full force and effect notwithstanding any termination of your use of our Site.
TERMINATION
You understand and agree that Miramax may, in its sole discretion and at any time, terminate or temporarily suspend your rights under any licenses describer herein and otherwise your access to our Site, and discard, remove, and/or disable or deactivate any or all of your Invited Submissions that you submitted to or by means of our Site and/or any other information and data that you (and/or anyone else) may have provided to or by means of our Site, for any reason. Miramax may also, in its sole discretion and at any time, discontinue our Site or any parts thereof or limit or restrict any user access thereto, for any reason, with or without notice. YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT Miramax MAY TAKE ANY ONE OR MORE OF THESE ACTIONS WITHOUT ANY NOTICE TO YOU, PRIOR OR OTHERWISE, AND YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT Miramax SHALL NOT HAVE ANY LIABILITY TO YOU OR TO ANY OTHER PERSON FOR ANY TERMINATION OF YOUR (OR ANYONE ELSE'S) ACCESS TO OUR SITE OR PARTS THEREOF AND/OR THE REMOVAL, DISCARDING, DISABLING OR DEACTIVATION OF ANY OF YOUR INVITED SUBMISSIONS (OR THE INVITED SUBMISSIONS OF ANYONE ELSE) OR THE REMOVAL, DISCARDING, DISABLING OR DEACTIVATION OF ANY OTHER INFORMATION OR DATA THAT YOU (OR ANYONE ELSE) MAY HAVE PROVIDED ON OR BY MEANS OF OUR SITE.
You may discontinue your access to, use or participation on or by means of our Site at any time.
INJUNCTIVE RELIEF
Notwithstanding anything to the contrary herein, you hereby irrevocably waive any right or remedy to seek and/or obtain injunctive or other equitable relief or any order with respect to, and/or to enjoin or restrain or otherwise impair in any manner, the production, distribution, exhibition or other exploitation of any Miramax or any Miramax affiliate-related motion picture, production or project, or the use, publication or dissemination of any advertising or promotion in connection with such motion picture, production or project. This provision shall remain in full force and effect notwithstanding any termination of your use of our Site.
CHANGES IN SITE OWNERSHIP
You will be deemed to have consented to the disclosure to, and use by, a subsequent owner or operator of our Site, of any information about you contained in the applicable Miramax database, to the extent Miramax assigns its rights and obligations regarding such information in connection with a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or some of Miramax's assets, or in connection with a merger, acquisition or sale of all or some assets related to a particular site, to a subsequent owner or operator. In the event of such a merger, acquisition, or sale, your continued use of our Site signifies your agreement to be bound by the terms of use and privacy statement of our Site's subsequent owner or operator. This provision shall remain in full force and effect notwithstanding any termination of your use of our Site.
These Terms of Use were last updated on November 12, 2019.
Miramax.com Privacy Policy
Last Updated: November 12, 2019
Thank you for visiting Miramax.com ("we" or "us"), a Miramax Film NY, LLC ("Miramax") Web site (the "Site"). Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the collection and use of the personal information you submit on this Site and other Web pages where this policy is posted.
THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT
At our Site, you can order products via our on-line vending pages; enter contests; vote in polls, respond to polls or surveys or otherwise express an opinion; subscribe to one of our services; register for sweepstakes, contests and other promotional opportunities; or participate in one of our online forums or communities. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services ("Personal Information").
At certain parts of our Site, only persons who provide us with the requested Personally Information will be able to order products, programs, and services, or otherwise participate in our Site's activities and offerings. We also collect certain anonymous, non-personally identifiable information when you visit our Site such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Firefox, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows XP or Mac OS), and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., AT&T, Comcast).
You can also engage with our content, such as video, games, applications, and other offerings (collectively, "Community Forums"), on or through (1) third-party social networking sites, such as Facebook, (2) third-party social media plug-ins and applications, and (3) Miramax social media plug-ins and applications that may be available through third-party sites or our Site.
When you engage with our content on or through third party social networking sites, plug-ins and applications you may allow us to have ongoing access to certain information from your social media profile (e.g., name, e-mail address, photo, gender, birthday, location, your list of friends, people you follow and/or who follow you, the posts or the 'likes' you make (collectively, "User Submissions") to deliver the content or as part of the operation of the application.
We may also obtain non-personally identifiable information (e.g., content viewed, game performance, high scores, and information about advertisements within the content you have been shown or may have clicked on, etc.) from your interaction with our content. During some visits we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse - overs), and methods used to browse away from the page. We may also collect technical information to help us identify your device for fraud prevention and diagnostic purposes.
When you provide information from your social media account, it can help enable us to do things like (1) give you exclusive content, (2) personalize your online experience with us within and outside our applications or websites, and (3) contact you through the social networking sites or directly by sending you the latest news, special offerings, and rewards from Miramax.
By doing so, you consent to the use of this information in accordance with this privacy policy.
When you provide personal information to us on our Site, on social networking sites (depending on your privacy settings) or through an application on social networking sites, it could be seen by anyone on the Internet.
Therefore, we cannot prevent further use of this information.
You can control what data you share through privacy settings available on some social networking sites.
To participate in certain Community Forums, you may be asked to select a username, screen name or member name and password. Please do not use your real name or the real name of another person when selecting a username (or screen name or member name).
For more information about how you can customize your privacy settings and how social networking sites handle your personal information, please refer to their privacy help guides, privacy policies and terms of use.
Note that anything you post to a Community Forum is public -- others will have access to your User Submissions and may use it or share it with third parties. Information you choose to post or make available in the community forums may be viewed, collected and used by others. If you choose to voluntarily disclose User Submissions, the protections of this Privacy Policy will not cover such disclosure of information. Think carefully before you post and use caution before disclosing any Personal Information.
Please also note that information submitted to our Site via a "contact us" or other similar function may not receive a response. We will not use the information provided to contact you for marketing purposes unrelated to your request unless you agree otherwise.
HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION
We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you.
This information allows us to communicate with you, such as to notify you when you have won one of our contests or when we make changes to our subscriber agreements, to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter, or to contact you about your account with us.
The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs, or services.
In addition, we may use information collected through our Site, including Personal Information, in order to: (1) process your registration, including, at times, verifying that the e-mail address you provide is active and valid; (3) provide you with information that you have requested or agreed to receive; (4) improve our Site and for internal business purposes; (5) contact you with regard to your use of our Site, your account, and, in our discretion, changes to any Miramax policy; and (6) for purposes disclosed at the time you provide your Personal Information or otherwise with your consent.
If you choose to submit content for publication (e.g., a "letter to our editors"), we may publish your screen name and other information you have provided to us. We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our Site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze usage of our Site, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services.
We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. In addition, we may transfer information about you if we or one of our business units are acquired by, sold to, or merged with another company.
Agents and contractors of Miramax who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for Miramax.
Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.
At some places on our Site, we may ask your permission to disclose personally identifiable information about you to companies whose practices are not covered by this Privacy Policy (e.g., other marketers, magazine publishers, retailers, participatory databases and non-profit organizations) that want to market products or services to you. If at some point you grant us permission to transfer your information for these purposes and later decide that you no longer want us to do so, simply log into your profile if you have created an account with us at our Site, or contact us here, and we will edit your preferences accordingly.
We may, on occasion, combine information we receive online with outside records to enhance our ability to market to you those products or services that may be of interest to you.
We provide you with an opportunity to express your preferences with respect to receiving details about other products and services from Miramax and other affiliated businesses and about products and services from selected third parties when you interact with our Site. If you ever decide in the future that you would like to update these preferences, you may log into your account if you have created one with us or you may contact us here and we will edit your preferences accordingly.
Finally, we will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses.
COLLECTION OF INFORMATION BY THIRD PARTY SITES AND SPONSORS
Some of our Site contains links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. For instance, clicking on an advertisement or on links or other elements on our Site may take you to an entirely different site. Links to other sites may use our Site logo or style as a result of a co-branding agreement. These sites may send their own cookies to you and may collect data and make use of that data in ways that our Site would not. Once you've left our Site, this Privacy Policy will no longer apply to Personal Information or any other data collected from or provided by you. You should check the applicable privacy policy to determine how that site will handle such data.
Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy policies before submitting any information, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.
We sometimes may offer content or programs (e.g., contests, sweepstakes, or promotions) that are sponsored by or co-branded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in our Site activity. We have no control over these third parties' use of this information.
Our Site will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if these third parties will obtain such information.
Our Site may include third-party advertising and reputable third parties, websites, advertisers, or the Internet advertising companies that work on their behalf, may present or serve the advertisements, provide us with data collection, reporting and ad response measurement, as well as assist with delivery of relevant marketing messages and advertisements. They automatically receive your IP (Internet Protocol) address when this happens. These third parties may view, edit, or set their own cookies (explained below) or use Javascript, Pixel Tags and other technologies to deliver advertisements, collect information about the effectiveness of their advertisements, and to collect anonymous information about your visits to our Site, such as the number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other Personal Information). The use of these technologies by these third parties is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by this privacy statement.
COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNICAL INFORMATION
We, our third party service providers, and our partners may send "cookies" to your computer or use similar technologies to enhance your online experience at our Site and across the Internet. "Cookies" are files that can identify you as a unique customer and store your personal preferences as well as technical information (including click through and click stream data). More specifically, Cookies are small data files that write to your hard drive for record keeping purposes when you visit us.
Cookies manage and measure the performance of advertisements displayed on or delivered by or through Miramax and/or other networks or sites.
Cookies can either be permanent (i.e., they remain on your computer until you delete them) or temporary (i.e., they last only until you close your browser).
We may also use "Web beacons" that monitor your use of our Site. Web beacons (or Web bugs) are small strings of code that provide a method for delivering a graphic image on a Web page for the purpose of transferring data, such as the IP address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the Web beacon appears, the URL (Uniform Resource Locator) of the page on which the Web beacon appears, the time the page containing the Web beacon was viewed, the types of browser that fetched the Web beacon and the identification number of any cookie on the computer previously placed by that server. When corresponding with you via HTML capable e-mail, Web beacons let us know whether you received and opened our e-mail.
In addition, we may use a service that collects data remotely by using so-called "pixel tags," "clear GIFs" or similar means (collectively, "Pixel Tags") embedded in our Site's content. A Pixel Tag is an electronic image, often a single pixel (1x1), that is ordinarily not visible to Site visitors and may be associated with cookies on the visitors' hard drives.
On their own, cookies Web beacons, or Pixel Tags do not contain or reveal any personally identifiable information. However, if you choose to furnish personally identifiable information, this information can be linked to the data stored in the cookies, Web beacons or Pixel Tags.
By accepting this Privacy Policy, you specifically agree to our use of cookies, Web beacons and Pixel Tags as described herein. You may adjust your browser to reject cookies from us or from any other Web site. Additionally, by setting your Web browser to display HTML e-mails as text only, you may be able to prevent the use of some Web beacons. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information. However, certain areas of our Site can only be accessed in conjunction with cookies or similar devices and you should be aware that disabling cookies or similar devices might prevent you from accessing some of our content.
OUR COMMITMENT TO SECURITY
We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online. However, no electronic data transmission or storage of information can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Please note that we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you use our Site and provide us with your information at your own risk.
HOW YOU CAN ACCESS OR CORRECT INFORMATION
To access the personally identifiable information that this Site has collected about you online from the pages on which this Privacy Policy is posted, to correct factual errors in such information, or to update your interests, preferences or other portions of your user profile, please log into your profile if you have created one with us or contact us here.
To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
ADDITIONAL INFORMATION REGARDING CHILDREN'S PRIVACY
Visitors to this Site may participate in many activities without providing any personally identifiable information. However, if a user wants to participate in certain of our interactive features, we ask the user to register and provide us with the following information: the user's e-mail address and age information. When the person who registers indicates that he or she is under 13 years old, we will either (i) collect no personally identifiable information from that individual, (ii) inform the child that a parent's verifiable consent is required, or (iii) collect the e-mail address of the user's parent in addition to the user's e-mail address. We use the parent's e-mail address to seek the parent's verifiable consent or notify the parent of his/her child's online activities and enable the parent to unsubscribe his/her child from a newsletter or other similar activity. If a user is under the age of 13, we will not condition his/her participation in an online activity on the disclosure of more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in the activity. We do not share children's information with outside third parties not bound by this Privacy Policy for their own marketing purposes. If you would like to review any personally identifiable information that we have collected online from your child, have this information deleted, and/or request that there be no further collection or use of your child's information or if you have questions about these information practices, you may contact us here.
INTERNATIONAL TRANSFER
As we operate internationally, and many of our computer systems are currently based in the United States, your personal data will be processed by us in the U.S. where data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world, such as the European Union and Canada.
Other than as set out below, if you create a user account with this Site as a visitor from outside the United States, you consent to the collection and/or processing in the United States of your personally identifiable information, which includes the use of cookies as described above.
Our Use of Content
Miramax will consider anything you provide to Miramax and/or contribute to this Site as available for our use free of any obligations to you, except where solicited Invited Submissions are expressly governed by Additional Terms appearing elsewhere on this Site (see Submissions, Postings and E-mails above), in which event those Additional Terms will determine how we will treat your Invited Submissions.
Subject to the provisions of any Additional Terms, by posting or uploading any content to this Site and/or providing any communication or material to Miramax ("User Content"), you automatically and irrevocably: (a) grant and assign to Miramax a royalty-free, perpetual, non-exclusive, unrestricted, worldwide license to any and all rights in the User Content including without limitation all copyright, together with all consents (if any) necessary to enable its reproduction, distribution, modification, publishing and/or other exploitation by Miramax and/or by any person authorized by Miramax, by any means and in all media now known or hereafter devised, without payment or other reference to you or any other person, and to advertise and promote such exploitation, for the full period of all such rights (together with any extensions and renewals) and insofar as possible in perpetuity; (b) waive all moral rights in the User Content which may be available to you in any part of the world and confirm that no such rights have been asserted; (c) appoint Miramax as your agent with full power to enter into any document and/or do any act Miramax may consider appropriate to confirm the grant and assignment, consent and waiver set out above; (d) warrant that you are the owner of the User Content and entitled to enter into these Terms of Use; and (e) confirm that no such User Content will be subject to any obligation, of confidence or otherwise, to you or any other person and that Miramax shall not be liable for any use or disclosure of such User Content.
DATA CONTROLLER
Where we decide the purpose or means of the processing of the Personal Information that you provide when using our Site, we are the ‘data controller’ for the purposes of the General Data Protection Regulation 2016 and the supplementary laws of EEA Member States.
LAWFUL BASES FOR PROCESSING
We process your Personal Information on the basis that it is necessary for the performance of a contract we have entered with you, or for us to comply with a legal obligation applicable to us.
We also process your Personal Information where it is in our legitimate interest to do so, such as the promotion and operation of our business or for the protection of others, but only when we have ensured this does not disproportionately impact your privacy.
YOUR RIGHT TO OBJECT TO PROCESSING
You can ask us to restrict, stop processing, or to delete your Personal Information if:
you consented to us processing the Personal Information, and have withdrawn that consent;
we no longer need to process that Personal Information for the reason it was collected;
we are processing that Personal Information because it is in the public interest or it is in order to pursue a legitimate interest of Miramax or a third party, you don’t agree with that processing, and there is no overriding legitimate interest for us to continue processing it;
the Personal Information was unlawfully processed;
you need the Personal Information to be deleted in order to comply with legal obligations; and
the Personal Information is processed in relation to the offer of a service to a child.
YOUR OTHER RIGHTS IN RELATION TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
You have the following rights over th]e way we process Personal Information relating to you.
We aim to comply without undue delay, and within one month at the latest, in response to any requests by you:
for a copy of Personal Information we are processing about you;
to have inaccuracies corrected;
to restrict, stop processing, or to delete your Personal Information;
for a machine readable copy of your Personal Information, which you can use with another service provider. Where it is technically feasible, you can ask us to send this Information directly to another provider if you prefer; and
to make a complaint to a data protection regulator.
You may contact them at: https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en
To make a request in relation to any of these rights, please send your requests to legal@miramax.com.
INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
We operate worldwide and the Information that we collect directly from you will be stored in our servers in the United States. We may also transfer your Personal Information to members of our third party service providers, many of whom may be located outside of the EEA, operate from multiple locations including non-EU based operations or engage sub-processors located outside the EEA.
We only transfer Personal Information outside of the EEA having implemented appropriate safeguards or where the receiving country is recognised as offering adequate protection.
RETENTION PERIODS
We will hold your Personal Information for as long as is necessary for the purpose for which that Information was obtained.
NOTIFICATION REGARDING UPDATES
From time to time, we may update this privacy notice and we encourage you to periodically check back and review this policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it.
We may revise this Privacy Policy to reflect industry initiatives, changes in the law or technology, or changes in our practices regarding information collection and use. If we make revisions to the way we collect or use Personal Data, we may provide notice of those changes by either: (1) announcing the change on the home page of our Site or (2) taking such other action as we deem appropriate under the circumstances, including without limitation, posting the revised draft of this Privacy Policy on our Site. You can determine when this Privacy Policy was last revised by referring to the "Last Updated" legend at the top of this page. Any changes to this policy will become effective upon posting of the revised Privacy Policy on the Internet, accessible through our Site. By continuing to use our Site following such changes, you will be deemed to have agreed to such changes. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, as it may be amended from time to time, in whole or in part, please do not continue using this Site.
HOW TO CONTACT US
If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or its implementation you may contact us here
